<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program CBACT01C based on the provided COBOL code:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
CBACT01C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of CBACT01C is to read and print account data from an indexed file. It sequentially reads records from the ACCTFILE and displays the account information for each record.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates in the context of a card management system, specifically within the CardDemo application. It is part of the account data processing workflow, likely used for auditing, reporting, or data verification purposes in a financial services environment.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. File Handling: The program opens, reads, and closes an indexed file (ACCTFILE) containing account records.
2. Sequential Processing: It sequentially reads through all records in the ACCTFILE until the end of the file is reached.
3. Data Display: For each account record read, the program displays detailed account information including account ID, status, balance, credit limits, and important dates.
4. Error Handling: The program includes error checking for file operations and displays appropriate error messages.
5. Abend Handling: In case of severe errors, the program has a mechanism to abend with a specific code (999).
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. ACCTFILE: This is an indexed file containing account records. The program reads this file sequentially to process and display account information.

Output Files:
N/A

Miscellaneous Input:
N/A

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Console Output: The program displays account information for each record read from ACCTFILE. This includes details such as account ID, active status, current balance, credit limits, and various dates associated with the account.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems. It operates independently, reading from the ACCTFILE and outputting to the console.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
