<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program CBACT03C based on the provided COBOL code:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
CBACT03C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of CBACT03C is to read and print account cross-reference data from an indexed file. It sequentially reads records from the XREFFILE and displays them.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates in the context of a card management system, specifically dealing with account cross-reference data. It's part of the CardDemo application, which likely handles various aspects of credit card account management and reporting.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. File Handling: The program opens, reads, and closes an indexed file (XREFFILE-FILE) containing account cross-reference data.
2. Sequential Processing: It sequentially reads records from the XREFFILE-FILE using the READ statement.
3. Data Display: Each record read from the file is displayed using the DISPLAY statement, showing the CARD-XREF-RECORD.
4. Error Handling: The program includes error handling for file operations, displaying appropriate messages and aborting the program if errors occur.
5. End-of-File Detection: It detects the end of the file and terminates the reading process when all records have been processed.
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. XREFFILE-FILE: This is an indexed file containing account cross-reference data. The program reads this file sequentially to process and display the records.

Output Files:
N/A

Miscellaneous Input:
N/A

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Console Output: The program displays each record read from the XREFFILE-FILE on the console, providing a visual representation of the account cross-reference data.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems beyond file I/O operations.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
