<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program CBACT02C based on the provided COBOL code:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
CBACT02C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of CBACT02C is to read and print card data from an indexed file. It sequentially reads records from the CARDFILE and displays them.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates in the context of a card management system, likely for a financial institution or a credit card company. It is part of the CardDemo application, which presumably handles various aspects of credit card data processing and management.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. File Handling: The program opens, reads, and closes an indexed file named CARDFILE-FILE.
2. Sequential Record Processing: It sequentially reads records from the CARDFILE-FILE until the end of the file is reached.
3. Data Display: Each record read from the file is displayed, presumably for review or verification purposes.
4. Error Handling: The program includes error handling for file operations, displaying specific error messages and file statuses in case of issues.
5. Copybook Usage: It incorporates a copybook named CVACT02Y, which contains the structure of the CARD-RECORD.
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. CARDFILE-FILE: This is an indexed file that contains card data records. The program reads this file sequentially to process and display card information.

Output Files:
N/A

Miscellaneous Input:
N/A

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Console Output: The program displays each card record read from the CARDFILE-FILE on the console, allowing for visual inspection of the card data.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems. It operates independently, reading from a local file and outputting to the console.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
