<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program CBACT04C.cob:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
CBACT04C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of CBACT04C is to calculate interest for credit card accounts. It processes transaction category balances, computes interest based on account-specific rates, and generates interest transactions.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates in the context of a credit card processing system, specifically in the financial calculations and account management domain. It is part of the interest calculation and posting workflow, which is a critical component of credit card account management and billing processes.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. Transaction Category Balance Processing: The program reads transaction category balances from the TCATBAL-FILE (FD-TRAN-CAT-BAL-RECORD) sequentially.

2. Account Information Retrieval: For each unique account, it retrieves account details from the ACCOUNT-FILE (ACCOUNT-RECORD) and cross-reference information from the XREF-FILE (CARD-XREF-RECORD).

3. Interest Rate Determination: It fetches the appropriate interest rate from the DISCGRP-FILE (DIS-GROUP-RECORD) based on the account group and transaction category.

4. Interest Calculation: The program calculates monthly interest (WS-MONTHLY-INT) for each transaction category balance using the retrieved interest rate.

5. Interest Transaction Generation: It creates interest transactions and writes them to the TRANSACT-FILE (TRAN-RECORD).

6. Account Balance Update: After processing all transaction categories for an account, it updates the account balance in the ACCOUNT-FILE to reflect the total interest (WS-TOTAL-INT) calculated.
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. TCATBAL-FILE: Contains transaction category balances for each account. This file provides the base amounts on which interest is calculated.
2. XREF-FILE: Stores cross-reference information linking card numbers to account IDs. It's used to retrieve the card number associated with each account.
3. DISCGRP-FILE: Contains interest rate information for different account groups and transaction categories. This file is crucial for determining the correct interest rate to apply.
4. ACCOUNT-FILE: Stores account information including current balances. It's read to get account details and updated with new balances after interest calculation.

Output Files:
1. TRANSACT-FILE: The program writes generated interest transactions to this file. Each record represents an interest charge for a specific account and transaction category.
2. ACCOUNT-FILE: This file is also an output as the program updates account balances with the calculated interest.

Miscellaneous Input:
1. EXTERNAL-PARMS: Contains the processing date (PARM-DATE) used for generating transaction IDs.

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Display messages: The program outputs various status and error messages to the console for monitoring and debugging purposes.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems beyond the files it processes. It operates as a standalone batch process within the credit card processing system.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
