<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program CBCUS01C based on the provided COBOL code:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
CBCUS01C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of CBCUS01C is to read and print customer data from a customer file. It sequentially reads records from an indexed file and displays each customer record.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates in the context of customer data management for a card demo application. It's part of a process that involves accessing and displaying customer information, which could be used for various purposes such as customer service, data verification, or reporting.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. File Handling: The program opens, reads, and closes an indexed file (CUSTFILE-FILE) containing customer records.
2. Sequential Record Processing: It sequentially reads customer records until the end of the file is reached.
3. Data Display: Each customer record read from the file is displayed.
4. Error Handling: The program includes error handling for file operations, displaying specific messages for different error scenarios.
5. Copybook Usage: It incorporates a copybook (CVCUS01Y) that defines the structure of the customer record.
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. CUSTFILE-FILE: This is an indexed file containing customer records. The program reads this file sequentially to access customer data.

Output Files:
N/A

Miscellaneous Input:
N/A

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Display Output: The program displays each customer record read from the CUSTFILE-FILE. This output serves to present the customer data to the user or for further processing.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems. It operates independently, reading from a local file and displaying the output.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
