<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program CBTRN03C.cob:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
CBTRN03C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of CBTRN03C is to print a detailed transaction report. It processes transaction records, cross-references them with account information, and generates a formatted report containing transaction details and totals.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates in the context of a credit card transaction processing system, specifically within the CardDemo application. It is part of the reporting workflow, generating a daily transaction report that provides insights into credit card transactions for a specified date range.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. Date Range Processing: The program reads date parameters (WS-START-DATE and WS-END-DATE) to filter transactions within a specific date range.

2. Transaction Processing: It reads transaction records (TRAN-RECORD) from the TRANSACT-FILE and processes them sequentially.

3. Cross-referencing: The program uses the XREF-FILE to look up account information (XREF-ACCT-ID) associated with each card number (TRAN-CARD-NUM).

4. Transaction Type and Category Lookup: It uses TRANTYPE-FILE and TRANCATG-FILE to retrieve descriptions for transaction types and categories.

5. Report Generation: The program writes detailed transaction information to the REPORT-FILE, including transaction ID, account ID, type, category, source, and amount.

6. Totals Calculation: It calculates and reports page totals (WS-PAGE-TOTAL), account totals (WS-ACCOUNT-TOTAL), and grand totals (WS-GRAND-TOTAL) for the transactions.

7. Pagination: The program manages report pagination, writing headers and totals at appropriate intervals (WS-PAGE-SIZE).
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. TRANSACT-FILE: Contains the transaction records to be processed and reported.
2. XREF-FILE: Stores cross-reference information linking card numbers to account IDs.
3. TRANTYPE-FILE: Contains descriptions for different transaction types.
4. TRANCATG-FILE: Stores descriptions for transaction categories.
5. DATE-PARMS-FILE: Provides the start and end dates for filtering transactions.

Output Files:
1. REPORT-FILE: The generated transaction detail report, including transaction details and various totals.

Miscellaneous Input:
N/A

Miscellaneous Output:
N/A
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems beyond the files it processes. It operates as a standalone batch program within the CardDemo application ecosystem.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
