<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program CBTRN02C:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
CBTRN02C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of CBTRN02C is to post records from a daily transaction file to various other files, including a transaction file, account file, and transaction category balance file. It processes each transaction, validates it, and updates the relevant records accordingly.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates in the context of a credit card processing system, specifically handling daily transaction processing. It is part of the CardDemo application, which likely manages credit card accounts and transactions for a financial institution.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. Transaction Processing: Reads transactions from the DALYTRAN-FILE and processes them one by one.
2. Transaction Validation: Validates each transaction by checking the card number against the XREF-FILE and verifying the account details in the ACCOUNT-FILE.
3. Account Update: Updates the account balance and cycle credits/debits in the ACCOUNT-FILE based on the transaction amount.
4. Transaction Categorization: Updates the transaction category balances in the TCATBAL-FILE.
5. Rejection Handling: Writes rejected transactions to the DALYREJS-FILE with a validation trailer explaining the reason for rejection.
6. Transaction Recording: Writes valid transactions to the TRANSACT-FILE for record-keeping.
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. DALYTRAN-FILE: Contains the daily transaction records to be processed.
2. XREF-FILE: Stores the cross-reference information between card numbers and account IDs.
3. ACCOUNT-FILE: Holds the account information for each customer.
4. TCATBAL-FILE: Stores the transaction category balances for each account.

Output Files:
1. TRANSACT-FILE: Stores the processed and valid transactions.
2. DALYREJS-FILE: Contains the rejected transactions along with the reason for rejection.
3. ACCOUNT-FILE: Updated with new balances and cycle credits/debits after processing transactions.
4. TCATBAL-FILE: Updated with new category balances after processing transactions.

Miscellaneous Input:
N/A

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Console Output: Displays the number of transactions processed and rejected at the end of the program execution.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems beyond the files it processes. It operates as a standalone batch program within the CardDemo application.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
