<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the COCRDSLC program:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
COCRDSLC
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of COCRDSLC is to accept and process credit card detail requests. It allows users to view credit card details by entering an account number and card number.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates within the context of a credit card management system. It is part of the business process that handles customer inquiries and provides access to credit card information for authorized users.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. User Input Handling: The program accepts account number (ACCTSIDI) and card number (CARDSIDI) as input from the user.

2. Data Validation: It performs validation checks on the input data, ensuring that the account number and card number are in the correct format and are valid.

3. Card Information Retrieval: The program reads card information from the CARDDAT file using the provided card number.

4. Display of Card Details: It displays card information such as the name on the card (CRDNAMEO), card status (CRDSTCDO), and expiration date (EXPMONO and EXPYEARO).

5. Error Handling: The program includes comprehensive error handling, providing specific error messages for various scenarios such as invalid input or data not found.

6. Screen Management: It utilizes CICS BMS (Basic Mapping Support) to manage the user interface, including displaying and receiving information through the COCRDSL map.
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. CARDDAT: This file contains credit card information. The program reads this file to retrieve card details based on the input card number.

Output Files:
N/A

Miscellaneous Input:
1. User Input: The program receives account number and card number as input from the user through the CICS screen.
2. DFHCOMMAREA: The program receives data from the calling program through the DFHCOMMAREA, which includes information such as the previous program, transaction ID, and user details.

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Screen Output: The program sends card details to the user's screen, including the name on the card, card status, and expiration date.
2. Error Messages: The program displays error messages on the screen in case of invalid input or when card information is not found.
3. DFHCOMMAREA: The program updates the DFHCOMMAREA with information to be passed back to the calling program or to the next program in the flow.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems beyond the CICS environment and the files it accesses directly.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
