<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
COSGN00C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The primary purpose of COSGN00C is to handle the sign-on process for the CardDemo application. It presents a login screen to users, validates their credentials, and directs them to the appropriate menu based on their user type.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program operates within the context of a credit card demonstration application. It serves as the entry point for users accessing the system, ensuring secure access and proper routing based on user roles.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. User Authentication: The program accepts user ID (USERIDI) and password (PASSWDI) inputs and validates them against stored credentials in the USRSEC file.

2. Dynamic Screen Display: Utilizes CICS commands to display the sign-on screen (COSGN0A) with dynamic content such as current date, time, and system information.

3. Error Handling: Implements error checking for invalid user inputs and displays appropriate error messages (WS-MESSAGE) on the screen.

4. User Type Identification: Determines the user type (admin or regular user) based on the SEC-USR-TYPE field from the USRSEC file.

5. Program Flow Control: Uses CICS XCTL commands to transfer control to different programs (COADM01C for admin users, COMEN01C for regular users) based on user type.

6. Logging Functionality: Incorporates a logging mechanism to track program execution and aid in debugging (using ADD-PROGRAM-LOG).
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. USRSEC: This file contains user security information, including user IDs, passwords, and user types. It is used to validate user credentials during the sign-on process.

Output Files:
N/A

Miscellaneous Input:
1. User Input: The program receives user ID and password input from the sign-on screen (COSGN0A).
2. System Date and Time: The program retrieves the current date and time to display on the sign-on screen.
3. CICS Environment Information: The program obtains CICS-specific information such as APPLID and SYSID to display on the screen.

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Sign-on Screen: The program generates and displays the sign-on screen (COSGN0A) with dynamic content.
2. Error Messages: The program outputs error messages on the screen for invalid inputs or authentication failures.
3. Program Transfer: Based on user authentication and type, the program transfers control to either COADM01C (for admin users) or COMEN01C (for regular users).
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems beyond the CICS environment and the files it accesses directly.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
