<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Documentation>


<HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

Here's the high-level overview of the program COUSR02C:

<ProgramName>
<![CDATA[
COUSR02C
]]>
</ProgramName>

<MainPurpose>
<![CDATA[
The main purpose of COUSR02C is to update user information in the USRSEC file within a CICS environment. It allows for the modification of user details such as first name, last name, password, and user type.
]]>
</MainPurpose>

<BusinessContext>
<![CDATA[
This program is part of the CardDemo application, which appears to be a credit card management system. COUSR02C specifically handles the user management aspect of the application, allowing for the maintenance and updating of user records within the system.
]]>
</BusinessContext>

<KeyFeatures>
<![CDATA[
1. User Lookup: The program can fetch existing user information based on the provided user ID (USRIDINI).
2. Data Modification: It allows updating of user details including first name (FNAMEI), last name (LNAMEI), password (PASSWDI), and user type (USRTYPEI).
3. Data Validation: The program performs basic validation checks, such as ensuring that required fields are not empty.
4. User Interface Interaction: It handles screen interactions using CICS BMS, displaying and receiving data through the COUSR2A map.
5. Error Handling: The program includes error handling mechanisms, setting flags (WS-ERR-FLG) and displaying error messages (ERRMSGO).
6. File Operations: It performs read and update operations on the USRSEC file to retrieve and modify user data.
]]>
</KeyFeatures>

<InputOutput>
<![CDATA[
Input Tables:
N/A

Output Tables:
N/A

Input Files:
1. USRSEC: This file contains user security information. The program reads from this file to retrieve existing user data for modification.

Output Files:
1. USRSEC: The program writes updated user information back to this file after modifications are made.

Miscellaneous Input:
1. User Input: The program receives user input through the COUSR2A map, including user ID, first name, last name, password, and user type.
2. DFHCOMMAREA: The program receives data through the CICS communication area, which includes information about the program context and user selection.

Miscellaneous Output:
1. Screen Output: The program sends data to the COUSR2A map to display user information and error messages.
2. DFHCOMMAREA: The program updates the CICS communication area with information about the current transaction and program state.
]]>
</InputOutput>

<Integration>
<![CDATA[
This program does not interact with any external systems beyond the CICS environment and the USRSEC file. It is primarily integrated within the CardDemo application, handling user data management operations.
]]>
</Integration>



</HighLevelOverviewOfThisProgram>

</Documentation>
